Guide to the Sisterhood is Global Institute Records, 1963-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2002 RL.01185
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files Series, 1975-2004 and undated, 49 boxes
  - Membership Files Subseries, 1975-2001 and undated, 7 boxes
    - Current Members (Box M2)
      - Prado, Danda, Brazil, 1985-1999 (Box M5)
      - Rivero, Isel, Cuba, 1986-2001 (Box M5)
      - Sarabia, Anna Leah, the Philippines, 2000-2001 and undated (Box M5)
      - Shaaban, Bouthaina, Syria, 1992-2001 and undated (Box M5)
      - Shahani, Leticia Ramos, the Philippines, 1999-2000 and undated (Box M5)
      - Shefali, Mashuda Khatun, Bangladesh, 1995-2001 and undated (Box M5)
      - Shukla, Sonal, India, 1989-2001 and undated (Box M6)
      - Santo Antonio, Salameda, Portugal, 1998-1999 (Box M6)
      - Tadesse, Zenebeworke, Ethiopia, 1987-1999 (Box M6)
      - Taylor, Margaret, Papua New Guinea, 1990-1992 and undated (Box M6)
      - Titkow, Anna, Poland, 1985-1999 (Box M6)
      - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua, Uzbekistan, 1997-1999 (Box M6)
      - Vajrathon, Mallica, Thailand, 1988-1999 (Box M6)
      - Van Houwelingen, Flora, the Netherlands, 1997-1999 (Box M6)
      - Vega-Centeno, Imelda, Peru 1997-1999 (Box M6)
      - Wali, Sima, Afghanistan, 1987-2001 (Box M6)
      - Waring, Marilyn, New Zealand, 1979-1999, 4 folders (Box M6)
      - Yacoobi, Sakena, Afghanistan, 1990s-2001 (Box M7)
      - Zaccaria, Paola, Italy, 1985-1999 and undated (Box M7)
    - Former Members
      - Badri, Amna, Sudan, 1985-1989 (Box M7)
      - Bernard, Cheryl, undated (Box M7)
      - Berger, Renate, 1986 (Box M7)
      - Borja, Carola, undated (Box M7)
      - Slavenka, Drakulic, Croatia, 1986-1997 (Box M7)
      - Green, Rayna, undated (Box M7)
      - Ketting, Marianne, the Netherlands, 1986-1991 (Box M7)
      - Liljestrom, Rita, Sweden, 1990 and undated (Box M7)
      - Merola, Giovanna, 1988 and undated (Box M7)
      - Oudijk, Corine, 1985, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Pineda, Magali, 1986 (Box M7)
      - Quan, Stella, 1985 (Box M7)
      - Sanchez, Luz Hellana, 1986 (Box M7)
      - Sebestyen, Amanda, 1986-1992 (Box M7)
      - de Zelaya, Maria Lourdes Centeno (Box M7)
    - General
      - Clippings on members, 1980s, 1990s, 5 folders (Box M7)
      - Filled-in form letters, 1995 and undated (Box M7)
      - List of old members, 1989-1995 (Box M7)
      - Membership profile, 1989-1999 and undated (Box M7)
      - Questionnaire, update, 1993 and undated (Box M7)
      - Prospective members, Jirina Siklova, 1995 (Box M7)
    - Publications
      - Afkhami, Mahnaz, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Aidoo, Ama Ata, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Antrobus, Peggy, 1989-1990 (Box M7)
      - Ås, Berit, 1990 and undated (Box M7)
      - Caules, Sonia, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Drakulic, Slavenka, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Mamonova, Tatyana, 1990 and undated (Box M7)
      - Mernissi, Fatima, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Pietilä, Hilkka, 1990 and undated (Box M7)
      - Taylor, Margaret, 1990 (Box M7)
      - Waring, Marilyn, 1990-1993 (Box M7)
    - Publications, not-circulated, 1992-1993 and undated (Box M7)
  - Greta Hofmann Nemiroff Subseries, 1985-2003 and undated, bulk 1998-2001, 3 boxes
    These record files, created by Greta Hofmann Nemiroff, a long-standing member of SIGI who was appointed president in 1999, contain correspondence to and from Nemiroff, as well as administrative and personnel records from the late 1990s and on and materials related to SIGI’s activities after its move to Canada in 1999. Some of the documents gathered by Nemiroff predate her tenure as a president of SIGI. The subseries is organized alphabetically by category and therein alphabetically by folder title.
    - CIDA, French translation, 1998 (Box GHN1)
    - Correspondence
      - 2000-2001 (Box GHN1)
      - Antonius, Rachad, 2001 (Box GHN1)
      - Association de lutte contre les violences faites aux femmes, 1995 and undated (Box GHN1)
      - David Block and Ellen Block, 2000-2001 (Box GHN1)
      - External, 2000, 2 folders (Box GHN1)
      - Freedman, Maria, 2000 (Box GHN1)
      - re: SIGI, 1999 (Box GHN1)
      - Robin Morgan, 1987, 1999-2001 (Box GHN1)
      - Sheila Murphy, 2000 (Box GHN1)
      - Women's Studies at Carleton University, 1995 (Box GHN1)
    - Correspondence, announcements, articles, meeting minutes, 1985-1999, 3 folders (Box GHN1)
    - Financial papers, 1999-2000 (Box GHN2)
    - Funding
      - Ford Foundation, 2000 (Box GHN2)
      - General Electric Fund, 2000 (Box GHN2)
      - Global Fund for Women, 2001-2002 (Box GHN2)
      - ICHRDD
        - Afghan women, KPP and general support, 2000-2002 (Box GHN2)
        - Health education and Afghan women, KPP, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Proposal for general support, 2003 (Box GHN2)
    - Fundraising, 2002 (Box GHN2)
    - Meetings
      - General, 1999-2002 (Box GHN2)
      - Steering committee, 1999 (Box GHN2)
    - Move
      - Archives, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Atwater library, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Letters, re: the move, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Members, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Sally Bingham Center, 2001-2002 (Box GHN2)
    - Personnel
      - Mahnaz Afkhami, 1996 and undated (Box GHN2)
      - Kate Bullard-Sisken, 1997-1998 (Box GHN2)
      - Maureen Donaghy, 1999 (Box GHN2)
      - Eisenberg, Ann, 1998 and undated (Box GHN2)
      - Fassihian, Dokhi, 1998 (Box GHN2)
      - Gomez, Heather, 1997-1999 (Box GHN2)
      - Goyal, Rakhee, 1997 (Box GHN2)
      - Lichtenstein, Sonja, 1996-1997 (Box GHN2)
      - Memarsadeghi, Mariam, 1996-1997 (Box GHN2)
      - Vaziri, Haleh, 1996-1997 (Box GHN2)
    - Statement, re: Sept. 11, 2001
      - General (Box GHN2)
      - Robin Morgan (Box GHN2)
    - Proposals
      - One pagers, 2000 (Box GHN2)
      - Sakena Yakoobi, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - University of Ottawa, 2001 (Box GHN2)
    - SIGI institutional documents, 1995-1997 (Box GHN2)
    - SIGI participation and events
      - Aoua Ly-Tall, 2000 (Box GHN2)
      - Beijing + 5, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Canadian Council for Refugees, 2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Child soldiers, 1998-1999 (Box GHN2)
      - Israel program, undated (Box GHN2)
      - Female genital mutilation, 2000-2001 (Box GHN2)
      - Marche Mundial, 1998, 2001 (Box GHN2)
    - SIGI participation and events (Box GHN3)
      - Muslim women, 1999-1998 (Box GHN3)
      - Palestina, 2001 (Box GHN3)
      - Peace Cafés, 2001-2002 (Box GHN3)
      - Rights of Passage conference, 1997 Sept. (Box GHN3)
      - Vienna, 1998 (Box GHN3)
      - Violence project, 1998 (Box GHN3)
      - Women, peace, armed conflict, and disarmament, 2000-2001 (Box GHN3)
    - SIGI projects
      - 1999 (Box GHN3)
      - Afghan women, 2002 (Box GHN3)
      - Fisheries, 2001-2002 (Box GHN3)
      - Safe and Secure, 1998 (Box GHN3)
      - Violence against girls and women in Muslim societies, 2000-2002 (Box GHN3)
    - United Nation, Angela King, 2001 (Box GHN3)
  - Financial Papers Subseries, 1984-2004 and undated, bulk 1996-2001, 19 boxes
    Annual reports, accounting documentation, tax records, external audit reports, and other records of SIGI's financial transactions. The documents include bills, receipts, ledgers, and account books. Highlights of the subseries include the annual reports, which provide summaries of SIGI’s activities and ongoing projects such as Human Rights Education (HRE), Violence against Women (VAW), and the Knowledge Partnership Program (KPP). Miscellaneous, unsorted documents are filed under Routine transactions, and can include records of administrative expenses, reimbursement, and invoices.
    Organized chronologically by year, then alphabetically by category within each year. Documentation from 2002 onward is sparse. Some folders contain data from preceding or subsequent years; this is indicated by the date span following the folder title. (Five electronic disks originally located in the records from 1996 and 1999 can now be found in the Electronic Formats Series.)
    - 1984 (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, Nov. (Box FP1)
    - 1985
      - Annual report, Mar. 1 (Box FP1)
      - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, June 16 (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit, 1985-1986 (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP1)
    - 1986
      - Annual report, 1986-1987 (Box FP1)
      - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit, 1986-1987 (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP1)
    - 1987
      - Budget, undated (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, June 9 (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box FP1)
        - SIGI taxes, 1987-1988 (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP1)
    - 1988
      - Budget, undated (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit, 1988-1989 (Box FP1)
      - Invitation, May 23 (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, May 16 (Box FP1)
    - 1989
      - Annual report, Feb.-Mar. (Box FP1)
      - Budget, undated (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit
        - General, 1989-1991 (Box FP1)
        - SIGI taxes, 1989-1990 (Box FP1)
      - General information, clippings, undated (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP1)
    - 1990
      - Annual report, 1990-1991 (Box FP1)
      - Budget, undated (Box FP1)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP1)
      - Financial, taxes, audit
        - General, 1990-1991 (Box FP1)
        - SIGI taxes, 1990-1992 (Box FP1)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP1)
      - Papers, meeting minutes, budget, undated (Box FP1)
    - 1991 (Box FP2)
      - Annual report, undated (Box FP2)
      - Budget, undated (Box FP2)
      - Financial, taxes, audit
        - General, 1991-1992 (Box FP2)
        - SIGI taxes, 1990-1992 (Box FP2)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP2)
      - Translation from Arabic, undated (Box FP2)
    - 1992
      - Alerts, undated (Box FP2)
      - Annual report, undated (Box FP2)
      - Budget, undated (Box FP2)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 4 (Box FP2)
      - Financial, taxes, audit
        - General, undated (Box FP2)
        - SIGI taxes, 1992-1993 (Box FP2)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP2)
      - Woman from Fiji case, undated (Box FP2)
    - 1993
      - Annual reports, undated (Box FP2)
      - Budgets
        - General, undated (Box FP2)
        - Apr. 1993-Apr. 1994 (Box FP2)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP2)
      - Financial, taxes, audit, undated (Box FP2)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP2)
    - 1993 (Box FP3)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Soheila Ainechi, 1992-1993 (Box FP3)
        - Opinion editorials, 1993-1996 (Box FP3)
      - Report of activities, 1993-1994 (Box FP3)
    - 1994
      - Annual report (Box FP3)
      - Audited financial statements, 1994 July-1995 July (Box FP3)
      - Budget (Box FP3)
      - Correspondence (Box FP3)
      - Financial statements, taxes, audit, 1994-1995 (Box FP3)
      - Meeting minutes (Box FP3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box FP3)
    - 1995
      - Annual report (Box FP3)
      - Audited financial statements (Box FP3)
      - Budget (Box FP3)
      - E-mail accounts, invoice, Oct. (Box FP3)
      - Financial statements (Box FP3)
      - Financial statements, taxes, audit (Box FP3)
      - Meeting minutes (Box FP3)
      - Meetings and events (Box FP3)
      - Routine transactions, Oct.-Dec., 3 folders (Box FP3)
      - Steering committee (Box FP3)
    - 1996 (Box FP4)
      - Annual report (Box FP4)
      - Audit
        - General (Box FP4)
        - Myint and Buntua (Box FP4)
        - NED (Box FP4)
        - NED, correspondence (Box FP4)
      - Bank reconciliation (Box FP4)
      - Beyond Beijing expenses, May, 3 folders (Box FP4)
      - Budget (Box FP4)
      - Budget and notes
        - After financial agreement (Box FP4)
        - General, 3 folders (Box FP4)
        - General ledger (Box FP4)
        - Rent agreement (Box FP4)
      - Checks deposited, Apr. (Box FP4)
    - 1996 (Box FP5)
      - Check requests, July-Aug., 2 folders (Box FP5)
      - Routine transactions, Jan.-Mar., 3 folders (Box FP5)
      - Check stubs, 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box FP5)
      - Coded checks, deposits, bank statements, for HOA, Sept. (Box FP5)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FP5)
      - Deposits
        - General, June-Aug., 3 folders (Box FP5)
        - Receipts for contributions, July (Box FP5)
      - Depreciation, undated (Box FP5)
      - E-mail, Mar. (Box FP5)
      - Fax activity report, June (Box FP5)
      - Financial, faxes, audit, undated (Box FP5)
      - Fax activity, e-mail, July (Box FP5)
      - Fax reports, postage by phones, Aug. (Box FP5)
      - Manual, correspondence with Khader, Oct. (Box FP5)
      - Meeting minutes, undated (Box FP5)
      - Routine transactions, Jan.-Mar., 3 folders (Box FP5)
    - 1996 (Box FP6)
      - Routine transactions, Apr., June, Nov.-Dec., 5 folders (Box FP6)
      - Statement of position, 2 folders (Box FP6)
      - Taxes
        - General (Box FP6)
        - 1099 info (Box FP6)
        - Copies of W2 forms (Box FP6)
        - Federal, 1996-1997 (Box FP6)
        - District of Columbia (Box FP6)
        - Maryland (Box FP6)
        - Maryland unemployment, SUTA (Box FP6)
        - Payroll worksheets (Box FP6)
    - 1997
      - Annual report (Box FP6)
      - Audit and tax returns, 1997-1998 (Box FP7)
      - Audit related documents, 1997-1998 (Box FP7)
      - Budget (Box FP7)
      - Claiming Our Rights invoices, unpaid (Box FP7)
      - Depreciation (Box FP7)
      - Financial statements, taxes, audit, 1997-1998 (Box FP7)
      - Meeting minutes (Box FP7)
      - Project invoices, Claiming Our Rights, paid 1996-1998, 3 folders (Box FP7)
      - Rent (Box FP7)
      - Routine transactions, Jan.-Mar., 3 folders (Box FP7)
    - 1997 (Box FP8)
      - Routine transactions, Apr.-Oct., 9 folders (Box FP8)
    - 1997 (Box FP9)
      - Routine transactions, Nov.-Dec., 3 folders (Box FP9)
      - Taxes
        - District of Columbia taxes (Box FP9)
        - Federal taxes (Box FP9)
        - State taxes, Maryland, 1996-1997 (Box FP9)
        - W2 forms, annual tax returns (Box FP9)
    - 1998
      - Annual report (Box FP9)
      - Audit, W2 forms, 1099 forms (Box FP9)
      - Audit related documents (Box FP9)
      - Audit report
        - Audit (Box FP9)
        - Tax return (Box FP9)
      - Budget (Box FP9)
      - Check stubs (Box FP9)
      - Claiming Our Rights invoices, unpaid (Box FP9)
      - Depreciation (Box FP9)
      - Financial statements, taxes, audit (Box FP9)
      - Invoices paid, workshops, Claiming Our Rights (Box FP9)
    - 1998 (Box FP10)
      - Meeting minutes (Box FP10)
      - Rent (Box FP10)
      - Routine transactions, Jan.-Aug., 9 folders (Box FP10)
    - 1998 (Box FP11)
      - Routine transactions, Aug.-Dec., 9 folders (Box FP11)
      - Taxes
        - Form 990, IRS tax return (Box FP11)
        - Quarterly 941 tax returns (Box FP11)
    - 1998 (Box FP12)
      - Taxes
        - 1998 taxes (Box FP12)
        - Virginia W/H tax form (Box FP12)
        - Unemployment insurance, Maryland (Box FP12)
    - 1999
      - Accountants, Raffa and Associates (Box FP12)
      - Accounting, funders (Box FP12)
      - Annual general meeting minutes, June (Box FP12)
      - Annual report (Box FP12)
      - Audit
        - Annual and audit reports sent to funders, letters (Box FP12)
        - Audit related documents (Box FP12)
        - Audit reports, 2 folders (Box FP12)
        - Auditors, Myint and Buntua, correspondence, audit info, 2 folders (Box FP12)
      - Check stubs (Box FP12)
      - Depreciation (Box FP12)
      - Finances, Riggs Repo account
        - Cash management services (Box FP12)
        - Repo account forms (Box FP12)
      - Income tax report (Box FP12)
      - Invoices, unpaid (Box FP12)
      - Lease, Atwater Avenue, Sept.-Oct. (Box FP12)
      - New York registration, 1998 documents (Box FP12)
      - Payroll (Box FP12)
      - Rent (Box FP12)
      - Routine transactions, Jan. (Box FP12)
    - 1999 (Box FP13)
      - Routine transactions, Feb.-June, 10 folders (Box FP13)
    - 1999 (Box FP14)
      - Routine transactions, July-Nov., 9 folders (Box FP14)
    - 1999 (Box FP15)
      - Routine transactions, Nov.-Dec., 3 folders (Box FP15)
      - SIGI, Canada finances (Box FP15)
      - State Farm insurance, policies (Box FP15)
      - State taxes (Box FP15)
      - Steering Committee meeting minutes (Box FP15)
      - Taxes (Box FP15)
      - Tax forms (Box FP15)
      - Tax receipt (Box FP15)
      - Unemployment insurance (Box FP15)
      - W2, W3, 1099, 1096 forms (Box FP15)
    - 2000
      - Accounting
        - Bank statements and miscellaneous receipts, 1999-2000 (Box FP15)
        - Bank statements, Canada (Box FP15)
        - Bank statements, United States (Box FP15)
        - Bills to be paid (Box FP15)
        - Checks and money to be deposited (Box FP15)
        - Deductions at source, statement of account (Box FP15)
        - Interest rate statements, US account (Box FP15)
        - Payroll (Box FP15)
        - Receipts of payment (Box FP15)
        - T4 application forms (Box FP15)
        - Transfers and wiring (Box FP15)
    - 2000 (Box FP16)
      - Accounting
        - VISA (Box FP16)
      - Budget, general, 2 folders (Box FP16)
      - Budget, May-Dec., 8 folders (Box FP16)
      - Expenses
        - Abco printing (Box FP16)
        - BCE, Mar.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP16)
        - Bell, Aug. Dec. (Box FP16)
        - Bell, Canada (Box FP16)
        - Ben Selinger (Box FP16)
        - Bernath, Janice (Box FP16)
        - Books (Box FP16)
        - Copelco (Box FP16)
        - DAS, Apr.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP16)
        - Denise Cotte, logo-graphiste (Box FP16)
        - Donations (Box FP16)
        - Federal, Jan.-July, Sept.-Nov., 2 folders (Box FP16)
        - Film Productions JG Inc. (Box FP16)
        - Fuller Landau (Box FP16)
        - General administration, Jan.-June, Aug.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP16)
        - Integlia + Integlia (Box FP16)
        - Konie, Gwendoline and Afifa Dirani Arsanios (Box FP16)
        - Le Groupe A+A (Box FP16)
        - Meldrum the Mover Inc. (Box FP16)
        - Moisan, Lise (Box FP16)
        - Pays, Jan.-July, Aug.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP16)
    - 2000 (Box FP17)
      - Expenses
        - Petty cash, Canadian, US, 2 folders (Box FP17)
        - Pilon, Natalie, Apr.-July, Aug.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP17)
        - Pitney Bowes leasing account statement (Box FP17)
        - Pitney Works (Box FP17)
        - Programs, consultants (Box FP17)
        - Rent, Feb.-June, Aug.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP17)
        - Research (Box FP17)
        - Resource center, magazines (Box FP17)
        - Swibel Novek (Box FP17)
        - Translation (Box FP17)
        - Travel (Box FP17)
        - VISA, Mar.-July, Aug.-Dec., 2 folders (Box FP17)
      - Income
        - Book sales
          - US, Jan.-Apr., May-Aug., Sept-Dec., 3 folders (Box FP17)
          - Canada, Jan.-Apr. (Box FP17)
        - Combined federal campaign, 2 folders (Box FP17)
        - Individual contributions (Box FP17)
        - International Center for Human Rights and Democratic Development (Box FP17)
        - McArthur Foundation (Box FP17)
        - Membership fees and renewal, 2 folders (Box FP17)
    - 2000 (Box FP18)
      - Income
        - Open file for foundations' contributions (Box FP18)
        - United Nations Development Fund for Women (UNIFEM) (Box FP18)
        - Various donations (Box FP18)
      - Income tax return (Box FP18)
      - Transactions to be entered or questioned, 1999-2000 (Box FP18)
    - 2001
      - Accounting
        - Bank statements, Canadian and US accounts, 2 folders (Box FP18)
        - Deductions at source, DAS (Box FP18)
        - Interest rates statements (Box FP18)
        - Payroll, 2 folders (Box FP18)
        - Transfers between accounts (Box FP18)
      - Budget
        - General (Box FP18)
        - Jan.-Dec., 12 folders (Box FP18)
      - Expenses
        - ABCO printing (Box FP18)
        - Alpha Laser International (Box FP18)
        - Bell Canada (Box FP18)
        - Bernath, Janice (Box FP18)
        - Books and subscriptions (Box FP18)
        - Citicorp Finance Vendeur, Ltée. (Box FP18)
        - Cotte, Denise (Box FP18)
        - Deductions at source, DAS (Box FP18)
        - Donations, 2000-2001 (Box FP18)
        - Editing, translations (Box FP18)
        - Federal Express (Box FP18)
        - Film Production JG, Inc. (Box FP18)
        - Fuller Landau (Box FP18)
        - Gaeten Boucher Transport (Box FP18)
    - 2001 (Box FP19)
      - Expenses
        - Gallagher, Flynn + Co., PLC (Box FP19)
        - General and administrative (Box FP19)
        - Integlia + Integlia (Box FP19)
        - Le Groupe A+A (Box FP19)
        - Meldrum the Mover, Inc. (Box FP19)
        - Membership in AQOCI (Box FP19)
        - Pilon, Natalie (Box FP19)
        - Petty cash, Canadian (Box FP19)
        - Postage by phone (Box FP19)
        - Pitney Bowes of Canada, Ltd. (Box FP19)
        - Pitney Works (Box FP19)
        - Rent (Box FP19)
        - Salaries (Box FP19)
        - Transfer between accounts (Box FP19)
        - Travel, conferences (Box FP19)
        - VISA (Box FP19)
      - Income
        - Abandon Productions (Box FP19)
        - Book sale (Box FP19)
        - The Favorite Game production (Box FP19)
        - Foundation contributions (Box FP19)
        - Individual contributions (Box FP19)
        - Membership (Box FP19)
        - Miscellaneous (Box FP19)
      - Lease (Box FP19)
      - Meeting minutes (Box FP19)
    - 2002
      - Annual report, audit, taxes (Box FP19)
    - 2003
      - Annual report, 2003-2004 (Box FP19)
  - Funding Files Subseries, 1984-2002 and undated
    The general administrative section in the series contains documents on the funding history of SIGI, together with correspondence, lists of potential sources, and guides on funding and proposal writing. Some correspondence and official statements date back to the founding and early history of SIGI in the late 1980s and early 1990s. The rest of the series contains project proposals submitted by SIGI and a large amount of brochures and print material related to individual foundations. Extensive documentation with correspondence and grant reports is available for major SIGI donors such as the Global Fund for Women, the Institute for the Study of Natural and Cultural Resources, John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, National Endowment for Democracy, The Shaler Adams Foundation, and UNIFEM. The subseries is organized alphabetically by name of organization, then chronologically.
    - A.J. Muste Memorial Institute, info, 1998 (Box FF1)
    - Administrative general
      - Articles on funding, 1993 (Box FF1)
      - Correspondence with Jasmine Schwartz, 1997 (Box FF1)
      - Cross-border charity, correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box FF1)
      - Foundation lists, 1984-1998, 2 folders (Box FF1)
      - Foundations, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box FF1)
      - Funding guidelines, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box FF1)
      - Funding history, 1984-1990, 2 folders (Box FF1)
    - Administrative general (Box FF2)
      - Funding history, 1990-1995, 2 folders (Box FF2)
      - Funding organizations prior to 1996 (Box FF2)
      - Funding requests to SIGI, 2000-2001 (Box FF2)
      - Funding status, 1996-2000, 2 folders (Box FF2)
      - HRE project, materials 2000, 2 folders (Box FF2)
      - KPP project, 2000
        - Afghan refugees, 2000-2001 (Box FF2)
        - Funding status, 2000 (Box FF2)
        - SIGI/Jordan funding proposal, 2000 Aug. 24 (Box FF2)
      - Letters of thanks to donors, 1995-2001, 4 folders (Box FF2)
      - Organizational history, 1999 (Box FF2)
      - Philanthropic organizations, info, 1999-2001 (Box FF2)